You there! Stop!
Stop thief! Police!
What's my number one rule?
The clients drink, you sip.
- Is Nishikawa-san upset with me?
- I'll take care of it.
Gargle and get back
out there. Okay?
Okay.
Joanna.
Nishikawa-san. Minami will be
right out. Next bottle's on me.
Thank you.
This is Joanna.
That is a beautiful suit.
- Another bottle?
- Of course.
Ohno-san, as I was saying.
I was thinking...
- Suzuki-sama.
- Yeah!
- Welcome to Club Polina.
- Good evening.
- This way, please.
- Thank you.
No skinny pours, Kenji.
Be generous.
We're watching you, Kenji.
You may be cute,
but we don't trust you.
Everyone.
Our two-month anniversary.
Kanpai.
I know how hard you've all been
working since we opened.
And while
there's room for improvement,
Minami...
You're all doing great.
Thank you.
And a special thank you to Club Polina's
number-one girl, Claudine.
Thank you, Mama-san.
- Have a good night.
- Good night.
Enjoy your afters.
- Stay safe.
- Okay.
- See you tomorrow.
- Good night.
Claudine, can I get
your help for a minute?
Did you see me with that big-spending
architect, Ohno-san? The man buys.
He's coming in again
tomorrow night.
- One of the girls is stealing.
- Are you sure?
Receipts don't match the inventory.
I'm down a million yen this month.
- What do you think I should do?
- I mean, find out who it is, right?
Then confront her.
Yeah. Makes sense.
So, why are you stealing
from me, Claudine?
Samantha, if half your customers are
here for me, it's not really stealing...
Is it?
I'm just taking my fair cut.
You'll start paying me back tonight.
Take it out of your pay.
It should take about eight weeks.
Really, you think I'm gonna
stick around for that?
You know who owns half of this club.
You cannot steal their money
and go set up shop
somewhere else.
Go ahead,
whistle for your thugs.
I'll tell them you don't know
how to keep track of their money.
I'll have the keys
to this place in ten minutes.
You're fired.
Fine.
I'm taking all my clients.
Especially that big-spending architect.
You're going to be fucked
without the money that I bring.
I'll take my chances.
You are like a tigress.
What? I can't give you
a compliment?
Not if it sounds like a bad
romance novel.
I have to go to work. So do you.
Quit the Meicho.
Come work for me at Shukan Forum.
What, you'd rather keep working
for Baku?
- That right-wing asshole?
- You're still holding that grudge.
Not a grudge, a fact.
The way he talks about Zainichi.
He doesn't do that
in front of me.
That's because he doesn't know
about you.
Shingo. The Meicho is my home.
Let's go away. This weekend.
Ryo's mother will take him
to baseball practice.
Your wife will do that for you?
Ex-wife.
It's her weekend.
So I'm free and clear.
I can't.
Your brother will be fine.
You know that's not true.
Bye.
Dad's 60th is in two months.
Mom's got a big thing planned,
and your presence is mandatory.
When you called and told Dad
you were thinking of coming home,
it really hurt him
when you didn't.
This is your chance
to make it up to him, okay?
And you should actually
make me a tape for once.
Because, Joshua, I'm the only person
in this world who actually likes you.
- What is he yelling about now?
- We do not know.
Is he still on you about that
Metropolitan Assembly piece?
He made me rewrite it twice.
Then reassigned it to Ichihara.
I read your piece
about the traffic fatality scam.
- It's good, Jake-san.
- Thanks, man.
Yeah, I just wish they hadn't buried it
all the way in the back.
You've started getting bylines
and you are complaining?
Jake! Now.
Your piece in this
morning's paper is good.
The last three months,
your work has been excellent.
Thank you, Maruyama-san.
I have what look to be two big stories.
You tell me which one you want.
Yeah, sure. Okay.
"Motorcycle thefts are way up.
Shinjuku, Asakusa, Shibuya."
A lot of our readers
ride motorcycles, even Baku.
Well, he rides a scooter.
What's the other one?
"Dead body found last night
in a pawn shop."
Police think he's yakuza.
I'll take the motorcycle story.
Make sure and get a quote
from a cop.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
The yakuza are ruthless men.
And this is a serious accusation.
Are you certain
you wish to make it?
COMPLAINT DEPARTMENT
Like I told you. My Hojicha tea
from Ibaraki never arrived.
Six bags. Who else but yakuza
would steal them?
Thank you for filing
your complaint.
We will, of course, investigate.
You'd better.
Do you also have a yakuza-related
citizen's complaint to file?
Actually, I'm on a story.
Do you know
anything about motorcycle theft?
You must have me confused
with a real policeman.
Please allow me to take my
esteemed friend for a coffee.
Is that a problem?
So, this is your new position?
"Organized Crime
Consultation Department"?
How much longer do you have to stay
there and take that punishment?
I was held officially responsible
for Miyamoto's death. So...
I must count myself lucky
I was not fired.
- How is your work, Jake?
- Good. Busy.
I'm keeping my nose clean.
As you said,
"Other crimes to be exposed,
other wrongs to be righted."
Any word on Tozawa?
The same.
You know, he tried to go
to the United States.
Then... nothing.
Have you received anything else
from whoever sent you that tape?
Then...
You have your work to do
and I have mine.
But...
After three months of silence,
perhaps the truth...
Is right in front of us.
If you think he's dead...
Why are Junko and the
kids still living out of town?
It's complicated.
I wish I could help you
with your story, Jake.
Well, it was a good excuse to get
you out of prison for an hour.
In this celebration of liberation,
we humbly ask Oyabun to speak.
Our brother Hayama has
returned from... "university."
We welcome back our brother.
Welcome back, brother!
Seven years in Fuchu.
Served on our behalf.
Starting today, he will serve
directly below me,
as wakagashira.
Hayama.
As the first son
of this family...
I will stand by your side.
My life dedicated
to our mission.
And Sato, having fully recovered
from his injuries...
Will resume his role as
wakagashira-daiko...
And will answer to Hayama.
I will do as my oyabun commands.
And what of Tozawa?
It's been three months since
anyone saw him.
And his gumi is quiet.
So what are we waiting for?
Tozawa-gumi without Tozawa
is a rotting house.
One kick and it'll collapse.
So we will take back Kabukicho
from them.
Luckily, we have you back.
You will lead this.
Oyabun, there will be retaliation.
We should be prepared.
I've been preparing
for seven years.
How old are you, baby brother?
Sato has earned our respect.
Don't treat him like a kid.
Oyabun, should we consider
procuring some "tools"?
Never. There is no honor
in guns.
My apologies.
If we fight it will be
eye to eye,
not at a distance like cowards.
Sato... Resume your duties.
Fill our coffers.
That is all. Understand?
Yes, Oyabun.
Dismissed.
Sato. There's something I need
you to do.
8F CLUB POLINA
- Hey!
- Hey! Hey, you were right.
This Minekawa Takako...
is the shit.
Oh, good. You know,
you could buy your own music.
Oh, with the price
you charge for drinks?
I gotta conserve my resources.
- So, how's business?
- Great.
Is being the big boss
everything you expected?
Just, you know, having
responsibility changes things.
Like what?
Like, I find myself
lecturing my girls on
not showing too much cleavage
and cursing so much.
This is you we're talking about?
I know, right? How about you?
Still avoiding the yakuza?
Yeah, still staying off
the sauce.
Actually, the work I'm doing now,
I can see it make a difference.
- Like, an actual difference.
- That's great.
I'm actually working on this big story
right now. Motorcycle theft.
I was wondering if you might know
anyone who might know anything.
Okay, now we get to the real reason
you just happened to stop by.
God.
Okay. Yeah. My...
my body guy in Ayase might...
possibly walk a little
in alternative markets.
No guarantees.
Watch yourself. Don't be stupid.
"Don't be stupid."
I'll have to remember that.
Thank you.
Just put it here.
Thank you
for filing your complaint.
If the yakuza try to steal your
cat again, please let us know.
Thank you so much!
Detective Funaki.
- Good to see you.
- You too, Katagiri-san.
Everything going well down here?
As well as could be expected.
The woman from
the National Police Agency...
Wants to talk to you.
What woman?
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
DEPUTY SUPERINTENDENT NAGATA
Come in!
Nothing.
Yes, today. Thank you.
- You asked to see me.
- Detective Katagiri. Have a seat.
I'm Shoko Nagata, from the NPA.
How may I be of assistance?
I need someone in this
department to work with me.
I hear no one knows the yakuza
better than you.
I see.
I also hear that you believe in keeping
balance between the factions.
Yes. I do.
That's bullshit.
Citizens lives are destroyed
by criminal debt.
Drugs flood the streets.
And we're supposed to keep
"balance"?
You would have them stabbing
each other in the streets?
Fine with me if yakuza
kill one another.
I see. What would you have us
do instead?
I have been authorized to create
a new task force
to combat organized crime
in Tokyo.
Using new strategies that have
proved very effective elsewhere.
How effective?
Effective enough that we can
smash the yakuza
in this city once and for all.
I need a partner.
Detective Katagiri.
Tell me you haven't been waiting
for this opportunity.
I wish you great success.
But I am not available
to join you.
How's school?
Good. It's hard.
It should be hard.
Did you like school?
School didn't like me.
I wanted to speak to you...
About money.
I gave you money last month.
I know.
But my tuition is going up.
And Father's pension is less
than Mother thought it would be.
Does she know you're asking me?
I don't have more to give you.
But I'm working on something.
If it pans out,
I'll have more for you.
What if I worked for you
instead?
Seriously. Let me earn it.
I'm a hard worker.
How good are you
with a computer?
Good.
Otsuka-san?
What?
My friend Samantha...
Owns a club in Akasaka.
Samantha.
Kawasaki Samantha? Okay.
Bring your bike by tomorrow.
I don't have a motorcycle.
Wait. She says you're the best
mechanic in Tokyo.
I'm a reporter.
Looking into why so many bikes
are stolen.
That's not news, is it?
Parts are worth more than bikes.
Bike companies only make enough
parts for their new models.
There are millions of
motorcycles in Tokyo.
Parts companies can't make that
many crank shafts, or whatever.
So where do you get them?
Every bike is an organ donor.
Worth more chopped up
than whole.
Any chance you could tell me
where I could find a...
Supplier of parts?
You're a friend of Samantha's?
Like a brother.
You do have skills.
- What are we selling?
- What?
Sneakers. I've got a warehouse
full of them in Yokohama.
Cool.
You're doing this with me.
Not Chihara-kai.
We finish this project,
that's it for you.
Understand?
Alright.
So how's this work?
A customer fills in
this order form.
Then the software sends them
an email
about where to wire the money.
Once the payment's confirmed,
your people ship the sneakers.
What?
There are no sneakers,
are there?
A sneaker store in Shinjuku
couldn't pay its loan back.
I took their inventory instead.
So this is legit?
Sorry to disappoint.
Now, will you explain
one more time?
Yabuki-san.
Please.
Why hasn't he called me?
Where is he?
That's not your concern.
Is he coming back?
- Is he... well?
- See her out.
Gentlemen, I commend you
on your choice.
Normally I recommend a single
malt be drunk neat...
But Glenmorangie improves
with a little ice.
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Ohno-san, I am so glad
you're here.
I've been hoping to talk to you.
That's very kind of you.
Is Claudine here?
Claudine has chosen to pursue
other career interests.
What a pity! She was always
a wonderful conversationalist.
To be honest, good conversation
is the minimum standard I expect here.
I'm afraid you might've
been shortchanged.
Allow me to personally remedy that?
Another time perhaps.
I hope to see you soon.
Good evening, Samantha-san.
Cool.
Is that a Suzuki?
All Suzuki?
Who the fuck are you?
Can I buy you guys dinner?
I'm a reporter for the Meicho.
Let's have a free meal.
Delicious.
- Give me some of that.
- Get it for him!
Tats, your bike's muffler
is crazy man!
Your bike is pretty lame.
I'd get a new one
in a heartbeat.
No way. He doesn't have
any money.
I can't believe
you'd say that.
Which came first, being friends
or riding motorcycles?
How much do they pay you
for an article?
You don't get rich writing
for newspapers.
So, how did you all start
hanging out?
How much do you pay us
for the article?
I can't pay you.
It's not allowed.
Then why the fuck
would we do this?
Because you'll look cool.
By being in a newspaper?
Hey sis, who reads newspapers?
Our grandfather does...
Oh wait.
He's dead.
She said it!
You're lying.
- My dear grandpa never said that.
- Shut up!
- You're wrong.
- Stop talking. Stop talking.
Thanks.
You can buy us dinner any time.
Until next time!
Hey. Gaijin.
You didn't leave enough
for the bill.
You trying to make us
look cheap?
That's all the money I have.
I didn't know you'd order
for twelve.
You calling us pigs?
- I didn't say that.
- Kick his ass, Tats!
Don't be stupid.
What did you say?
Tats!
You alright?
I'm fine.
You're alright, Meicho.
Okay, you can hang with us.
But no real names.
And you show me everything
you do. Photos too.
This gaijin's crazy.
We haven't paid yet.
Let's go back in.
One moment.
I'll be right with you.
Your place looks good.
Thanks.
I'm sorry
for not getting in touch.
Yeah.
I called a lot.
I know.
I went to your offices.
They said you were somewhere safe.
"Recovering."
They wouldn't tell me
anything else.
What happened?
Tell me.
A knife in the stomach.
It's okay. It turns out I have
very hard internal organs.
I'm sorry about your friend.
And for not doing more.
I'm sorry for expecting you to.
Are you taking over
for Kobayashi?
Good.
So, you came by to check in?
I came to tell you
that you must rehire Claudine.
- Excuse me?
- She must work here.
Sato, she stole from me.
- She's really fucked me.
- This is Oyabun's order.
Tell Ishida-san, the last time
that I checked, our contract...
as long as he gets his money,
I run the club the way I want.
Samantha.
You need to do this.
Trust me.
You need to hear
what I'm saying.
My club... my rules.
Thanks for stopping by.
I think Jake's story
could be a feature.
Bosozoku gangs are old news.
We've covered them plenty
over the years.
But no one's ever had access
to them like this.
The focus will be these kids.
Fallen through the cracks.
They trust you?
So far.
Okay. See where it takes you.
Thank you.
New batch.
Be honest.
- You made those?
- Last night. Butter cookies.
Dude! You're wasting
your talents here.
- I used a very light maple glaze.
- You're a rock star. Really.
Don't give all those away, okay?
Save me some?
- Don't give 'em all away.
- Sure.
Rock star.
Hello, Mama-san.
Hello, wild child.
I don't know what I would've done
if you hadn't hired me.
I knew you'd be a good hostess.
Club Destiny was a great place
to start.
Better than Club Onyx
you went to next.
- Am I right?
- Right.
I'm sorry that I left.
Just disappeared.
I'm really sorry.
Is this what those phone messages
were about months ago?
I called you back the next day.
Yeah. I meant to call you back again.
I'm sorry about that, too.
Thank you. I was angry.
But that's also
in the past now.
And look at you now, Samantha.
Five years on, your own club.
Good for you.
For you, too, Erika-san,
if you'd like.
I need a number-one girl.
I got out for a reason,
you know.
I'll give you half of all
your table charges.
Half of every bottle you sell.
Samantha,
you must be desperate.
Mama, I'm not tired anymore.
I want my pikachu.
I'll come and fetch him
in a minute.
Daichi. Say hi to my friend
Samantha-san.
Samantha-san?
She's a very important
business woman.
- Hello.
- Hello, Daichi. You are a very cute boy.
- She called you cute.
- I am cute!
I had no idea.
It was a surprise to me, too.
Just come tonight.
Same offer. Plus I'll pay for a sitter,
get you a ride home.
The girls are great. The place is great.
And I trust you.
What do you think, Dai-chan?
Should I take Samantha-san's money?
Take it.
Can I have some too?
Really?
Why do you speak Japanese?
Hello, Auntie.
Who the hell are you?
I know you.
Oyabun sends his regards.
Chihara-kai has no business here.
Shall we do that again?
What do you want?
The money you've been giving
the Tozawa-gumi every month.
This'll be twice a month.
And if I find out you're paying
Tozawa anything...
I come back and break all your
pretty boys' noses.
Yours too.
Tozawa won't stand for this.
Tozawa's gone.
His people come here,
you tell them Hayama is back.
Kabukicho belongs
to Chihara-kai.
You keep telling yourself that.
That's how you keep the order,
little brother.
Chihara-kai's gone soft
since I went away.
But Hayama's back now.
Look at you. So worried they're
gonna retaliate.
I fucking hope they do.
I look forward to it.
It's been three months.
Not a word.
And I have done nothing
to provoke his men.
The danger is passed.
You and the girls can come home.
Or you could retire
and move here.
And we would make this our home.
The girls love it here.
My new position keeps me from
any interaction with yakuza.
I'm sure, but...
Are you happy sitting there
all day...
Listening to old ladies'
complaints
until you retire?
That is what I thought.
You are a good man who always
wants to do the right thing.
But I cannot put the girls
at risk anymore.
So you need to think about what
the right thing is now.
- I like riding loud.
- Why?
Because normal people
fucking hate it
and want you to be quiet.
I'd rather get high, fuck girls,
and steal bikes
than live like them.
If I steal enough bikes?
I pay for my sister to get
a spot in private school.
Get her out of here.
Yeah?
Where?
Stay there.
Get on.
You want a story or not?
- You Kota's friend?
- Yeah.
Come in.
Tokarev. Holds eight rounds.
For you, three hundred thousand.
'Cause you're Kota's friend.
What do you say?
Hey!
Can you get more?
I thought you yakuza
didn't fuck with these.
Always good to be prepared.
Three hundred.
- And make this hallway narrower.
- Understood.
Hello!
Ohno-san.
It's Samantha, from Club Polina.
I seem to be very popular today.
- Claudine called me as well.
- Did she?
It seems she has decided to ply
her trade at a different club.
I see. Well... I have been seriously
considering your case
and have taken decisive actions
to retain your loyalty.
Which is why I have engaged
the most beautiful
and charming woman
in all of Tokyo
to dedicate herself tonight
to entertaining you.
This may be true,
but it isn't very modest of you.
I'm referring
to my good friend, Erika.
And it is, I promise you,
quite true.
That's hard to prove,
but I will come in,
and I'll give your place
another try tonight.
- I am very pleased to hear that.
- If you agree to grace my table.
No one else.
Just you.
My bike's around the corner.
You set your watch for thirty seconds.
That's how long you have
to drill the ignition.
- Okay.
- Any longer, you walk.
What are you doing?
Watch the street.
If anyone comes let me know.
I'm a reporter.
I can't aid in committing a crime.
But you can watch?
C'mon. Stop being a bitch.
Go, now. Hurry!
Don't piss me off.
The bike was over there.
Hey, do you lot know
where Roppongi is?
Where the girls and the clubs
and the bars are at?
I learned a Japanese song.
Hey. It's a good song.
It's a famous song, I bet you know it.
Maybe another time.
That's my motorcycle!
I have a joke for you.
- Can you gentlemen handle it?
- Of course.
Wait a minute. No...
I had no idea that investors
were so wicked.
- They are.
- Okay, what about you?
What are architects really like?
- Me?
- Yeah.
We are confidence men.
We convince our clients
we see the future,
that their building
will look beautiful,
that it will fit in its setting.
Okay, okay.
You know, I used to work for a man
who said hostesses sell dreams.
I don't think that's true.
So, what are you selling?
What am I selling?
A place where confidence men
can come and be honest.
Then, honestly...
this is the best evening
I've had in a long time.
Erika, you're hilarious!
Me, too.
I'm so glad.
Detective. You're here late.
Your new strategies.
What about them?
What do you need from me?
I need you to be done
with balance.
Yes.
Time to go home.
- A little extra, with my thanks.
- What?
- No, Samantha. It's too much.
- You're kidding.
You got Nishikawa-san to buy more bottles
tonight than he did in a week.
Honestly?
- I forgot how good I was.
- And you had fun too, right?
I did.
Hey,
I wanted to ask you earlier.
Who's your pretty friend?
Polina.
The club's named after her.
- She died. Three months ago.
- Oh, Samantha, I'm so sorry.
That night I left you
all the voicemails...
that was the night
I found out she died.
I called you because
I didn't have anyone else.
- No.
- So, I'm really glad you're here.
Me, too.
I need a locker.
Store some papers.
Help yourself.
No Saturdays. Your other girls
can do "losers night."
- And I want one night a week for Daichi.
- Fine.
I will take my number-one girl
as many nights as I can get her.
- Great.
- Sato-san.
Will you drive Erika-san home?
I have to stay and finish up.
Don't worry, I don't bite...
Much.
- Fine. Let's go.
- That's very kind of you.
- 'Night, Erika-san.
- 'Night, Mama-san.
IS THIS A REBELLION
AGAINST SOCIETY...
OR IS IT A CRY FOR HELP?
This is Adelstein.
I'm sending in my motorcycle
gang article now.
- Hello!
- It's me.
Would you like to come over?
- Hi.
I saw one of your articles
in yesterday's paper.
Yeah?
It was very good.
Thanks.
I wanted to call you after you came
about the Yoshino, but...
it wasn't safe.
Yeah, I figured.
That's why I stayed away.
I haven't seen or heard from him
in months
and his men do not seem
concerned with me anymore.
You know this is
a really bad idea, right?
Yes.